



□ +380935374841 | Main hi@shal.dev | Ashal.dev | In ashanaakh

"With hard work and effort, you can achieve anything."

Summary.

Currently Middle Golang Engineer at OpenWare. Two years of experience specializing in the backend, concurrency and microservices. Interested in devising a better problem-solving method for challenging tasks, and learning new technologies and tools. As for sport I like swimming and cycling. Travelling is my passion, I like to discover new places and inspire by amazing views.

Skill Highlights.

Programming Languages Golang, Ruby, Python, C++

Microservices Docker, Kubernetes Cloud Terraform, AWS, GCP Database MySQL, PostgreSQL, Redis Languages English, Russian, Ukrainian

Education

Taras Shevchenko National University of Kyiv

BACHELOR IN SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

• My GPA is 4.39/5

Taras Shevchenko National University of Kyiv

MASTER IN SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

Kyiv, Ukraine

2015 - 2019

Kyiv, Ukraine

2019 - PRESENT

Jan. 2019 - PRESENT

Dec. 2018 - PRESENT

Kyiv, Ukraine

Experience

OpenCars Kyiv, Ukraine

GOLANG ENGINEER

- Software designing and implementation
- · Telegram bot management
- Specifications development
- Deployment automation

OpenWare Kyiv, Ukraine

GOLANG ENGINEER • Writing idiomatic and resillient Go code

- Software architecture construction and designing
- Specifications and requirements development
- · Code review
- High loaded software development
- · Closely coached and mentored new project member

MyTimeTable Kyiv, Ukraine Jun. 2019 - Sep. 2019

DEVOPS

• Inftastructure as code development

- Implementation of docker images
- Implementation of CI/CD pipelines
- Managing project on DigitalOcean

Helios Technologies

DEVOPS & BACKEND ENGINEER

- Ruby on Rails Development
- Golang development
- Assembling components using Docker
- DevOps tools development
- Managing projects on Google Cloud Platform
- Build plugins for CI/CD tools
- Build advanced deployments using Kubernetes
- Development of complicated terraform modules
- Design & Implement in-cluster high-speed workers

Jun. 2017 - Dec. 2018

ALI SHANAAKH

Palestine Nights Al Muharrag, Bahrain Sep. 2018 - Dec. 2018

CO-FOUNDER & FULL STACK ENGINEER

- Software designing and implementation
- Specifications development
- Deployment automation
- Development of APIs
- Digital Ocean deployment automation

Program Committees

2018 **Team Member**, Google Hash Code Hackathon Kyiv, Ukraine Lisbon, Portugal 2018 Opensource Initiative Winner, Websummit 2019 Visitor, iForum Kyiv, Ukraine 2019 Visitor, IT Weekends Kyiv, Ukraine

ALI SHANAAKH